<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Uniwise</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="aboutp">
        <b>Why Uniwise exists?</b> \n Uniwise is an application developed for Government Polytechnic, Pune to share knowledge among students, that would be valuable and easily available to everybody. Currently, this knowledge is limited to only a few – either locked in their heads, or only accessible to select groups. We want students to interact with each other using our application as a medium to collaborate with each other to yield benefits to and from rest of the students.\n
        The heart of Uniwise is the questions &amp; queries that are asked by students. It can be shared by students from all divisions by creating their logins, selecting their respective departments and asking questions and posting answers in any form (audio, video, image, comment etc.). We intend to include content related to student’s curriculum &amp; courses. On the home page, you can also view all the current events and activities happening in the institute.  \n \n \n <b>Privacy Policies: -</b>
        \n Uniwise recognizes that your privacy is very important, and we take it seriously. Uniwise Privacy Policies describe our policies and procedures on the collection, use, and sharing of personal information while using the Uniwise platform. \n \n <b>Personal Information :</b> \n We collect user’s information automatically from the Uniwise platform. \n \n
        <b>Account and Profile Information:</b> \n
        When you create an account and profile on the Uniwise platform, Users name, Phone number, email and other information will be stored in our database for future use ONLY. User’s public name, photo, and other personal details and information will be added to the public-facing profile as per user discretion. This information can be viewed only by other users of the application. \n \n
        <b>Posted and Uploaded Content:  </b>
        \n The information and content posted on the Uniwise platform, including your questions, answers, photos, videos and comments will be collected and stored in databases.
        \n \n <b>Communication :</b> \n
        Your contact information will be used to communicate with you (via email, Phone no, from the Uniwise platform) \n \n
        <b>Delete/Deactivate Account:  </b>\n
        You can delete your account using the “Delete Account” option provided in the app.
        \n \n
        <b>Impressum   :</b>
        \n
        \n
        Government Polytechnic Pune., University Road,  \tPune. 411016\n\n
Email: <a href="mailto:anujajadhav2512@gmail.com">uniwise.gpp@gmail.com</a> \n \n
Phone: +91-20-25655907\n\n
Representatives:  Anuja D. Jadhav\n
\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t Suyash S. Bavlekar\n
\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t\t Tanaya S. Sakpal\n\n\n\n




</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
</resources>
